Betty Wilke Cox papers, Inclusive: 1896-2007, undated, Bulk: 1970-2006, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Personal Materials, 1896-2007; 3
  - Invitation to Inauguration of Ann W. Richards and Bob Bullock, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Journal, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Journal, 1954-1955 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Lansbury, Angela: Photographs, undated (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Legal Documents, undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Life Magazine, 1985 August (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Masters, Richard: CPR, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Medical Records (1 of 5) [REMOVED], 1998-2007 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Medical Records (2 of 5) [REMOVED], 1998-2007 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Medical Records (3 of 5) [REMOVED], 1998-2007 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Medical Records (4 of 5) [REMOVED], 1998-2007 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Medical Records (5 of 5) [REMOVED], 1998-2007 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Notes (1 of 18), undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Notes (2 of 18), undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Notes (3 of 18), undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Notes (4 of 18), undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Notes (5 of 18), undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Notes (6 of 18), undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Notes (7 of 18), undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Notes (8 of 18), undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Notes (9 of 18), undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Notes (10 of 18), undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Notes (11 of 18), undated (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Notes (12 of 18), undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Notes (13 of 18), undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Notes (14 of 18), undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Notes (15 of 18), undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Notes (16 of 18), undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Notes (17 of 18), undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Notes (18 of 18), undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Mexico Trip, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Outdoor School: Native American Tribes (1 of 3), undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Outdoor School: Native American Tribes (2 of 3), undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Outdoor School: Native American Tribes (3 of 3), undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Paisano, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Photographs: Betty Wilke Cox, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Photographs: Family and Friends (1 of 4), 1896-2004 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Photographs: Family and Friends (2 of 4), 1896-2004 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Photographs: Family and Friends (3 of 4), 1896-2004 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Photographs: Family and Friends (4 of 4), 1896-2004 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Photographs: Negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Resumes, undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Suburban Notebook, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Travel Documents (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Travel Documents (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - United Stated War Savings Bond, 1942 September 24-1943 September 25 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Family Documents, 1936-2007; 4
  This series is composed of correspondence, cards, and photographs related to several of Cox's family members such as her granddaughter, Hallie Cox, and her sister, Helen Wynn. However, the majority of the series contains materials pertaining to her son, Mike Cox.
  - Cox, Bill, 1936 December 29-1946 November 24 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Cox, Hallie, 1997-2003 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Cox, Hallie: Cards (1 of 2), undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Cox, Hallie: Cards (2 of 2), undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Cox, Linda, 1989 September 6-1999 December 17 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Cox, Mike: Articles (1 of 4), 1996-2000 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Cox, Mike: Articles (2 of 4), 1996-2000 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Cox, Mike: Articles (3 of 4), 1996-2000 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Cox, Mike: Articles (4 of 4), 1996-2000 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Cox, Mike: "Caige" Grimes, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Cox, Mike: Cards, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Cox, Mike: Correspondence (1 of 8), 1976 September 9-2007 February 9 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Cox, Mike: Correspondence (2 of 8), 1976 September 9-2007 February 9 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Cox, Mike: Correspondence (3 of 8), 1976 September 9-2007 February 9 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Cox, Mike: Correspondence (4 of 8), 1976 September 9-2007 February 9 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Cox, Mike: Correspondence (5 of 8), 1976 September 9-2007 February 9 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Cox, Mike: Correspondence (6 of 8), 1976 September 9-2007 February 9 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Cox, Mike: Correspondence (7 of 8), 1976 September 9-2007 February 9 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Cox, Mike: Correspondence (8 of 8), 1976 September 9-2007 February 9 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Cox, Mike: Literary Productions (1 of 6), 1996 January 1-2001 October 30 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Cox, Mike: Literary Productions (2 of 6), 1996 January 1-2001 October 30 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Cox, Mike: Literary Productions (3 of 6), 1996 January 1-2001 October 30 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Cox, Mike: Literary Productions (4 of 6), 1996 January 1-2001 October 30 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Cox, Mike: Literary Productions (5 of 6), 1996 January 1-2001 October 30 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Cox, Mike: Literary Productions (6 of 6), 1996 January 1-2001 October 30 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Cox, Mike: Notes, undated (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Cox, Mike: Personal Materials (1 of 4), 1955 August 1-1990 May 27 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Cox, Mike: Personal Materials (2 of 4), 1955 August 1-1990 May 27 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Cox, Mike: Personal Materials (3 of 4), 1955 August 1-1990 May 27 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Cox, Mike: Personal Materials (4 of 4), 1955 August 1-1990 May 27 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Cox, Mike: Saddlebag Books, 1995 September-1997 April (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Family Records, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Janet (Betty Cox's Niece), undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Wilke Family, 1993-1999 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Wilke, L.A. (1 of 2), 1978-1984 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Wilke, L.A. (2 of 2), 1978-1984 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Wilke, L.A. and Viola, 1979-1982 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Wilke, Viola, 1979-1981 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Wynn, Helen: Cards (1 of 2), undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Wynn, Helen: Cards (2 of 2), undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Wynn, Helen: Correspondence (1 of 5), 1975-2001 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Wynn, Helen: Correspondence (2 of 5), 1975-2001 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Wynn, Helen: Correspondence (3 of 5), 1975-2001 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Wynn, Helen: Correspondence (4 of 5), 1975-2001 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Wynn, Helen: Correspondence (5 of 5), 1975-2001 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Wynn, Helen: Paintings, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Wynn, Helen: Photographs, undated (Box 27, Folder 20)
- General Research, 1975-2003; 5
  This final series is a collection of research materials, including some correspondence, for a variety of subjects. None of the original folders specified what the research was for.
  - Baugh, Sam, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Civil War, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (1 of 3), 1994 March 28-2002 April 4 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (2 of 3), 1994 March 28-2002 April 4 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (3 of 3), 1994 March 28-2002 April 4 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Custer, Elizabeth and George (1 of 5), 1982 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Custer, Elizabeth and George (2 of 5), 1982 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Custer, Elizabeth and George (3 of 5), 1982 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Custer, Elizabeth and George (4 of 5), 1982 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Custer, Elizabeth and George (5 of 5), 1982 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Danenhauser, Matt (1 of 4), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Danenhauser, Matt (2 of 4), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Danenhauser, Matt (3 of 4), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Danenhauser, Matt (4 of 4), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Dayton (1 of 3), 2000 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Dayton (2 of 3), 2000 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Dayton (3 of 3), 2000 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Long, Huey, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Louisiana (1 of 4), 2001 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Louisiana (2 of 4), 2001 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Louisiana (3 of 4), 2001 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Louisiana (4 of 4), 2001 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Quote Permission, 1996 June 21 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Notes (1 of 2), undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Notes (2 of 2), undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Nut Bush Presbyterian Church, 1997 May 22 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Reference Notes-Judith, undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Sanctificationists (1 of 4), 1994 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Sanctificationists (2 of 4), 1994 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Sanctificationists (3 of 4), 1994 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Sanctificationists (4 of 4), 1994 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Sweden/Svante Palm, 1992 August 21 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Terry Texas Ranger (1 of 6), 1997 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Terry Texas Ranger (2 of 6), 1997 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Terry Texas Ranger (3 of 6), 1997 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Terry Texas Ranger (4 of 6), 1997 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Terry Texas Ranger (5 of 6), 1997 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Terry Texas Ranger (6 of 6), 1997 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Women on the Texas Frontier, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 22)